Atanas Konduzov

478 Youngwood Drive East Stroudsburg PA 18301

570-620-7918

ak3641@live.esu.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/ak3641/

PROFILE SUMMARY

Conscientious and achievement oriented individual committed to producing results above and beyond what is expected. Strong leadership and management qualities with over 5 years of experience as a catering captain with Aramark, tutor with Pennsylvania State System of Higher Education and Northampton Community College, and treasurer of the National Society of Leadership and Success. Recognized by faculty, peers, and co-workers for great time management skills and outstanding talent in analysis, strategy, and planning. Highly dedicated to professional growth and development.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Business Management

May 2013

Concentration: Management and Finance

Minor, Economics

East Stroudsburg University of Pennsylvania

• Major GPA: 3.74, Minor GPA: 3.83, Cum. GPA 3.56

• Dean's List

RELATED EXPERIENCE

Northampton Community College

October 2013 - Present

Professional Statistics Tutor

- Tutor and assist variety of students with statistical problems.
- Prepare students for exams by designing and providing sample questions for practice.
- Improve students' understanding of statistical concepts and help them with studying methods.

PASSHE (Pennsylvania State System of Higher Education)

September 2012 - May 2013

Student Tutor

- Mentored students taking QBA (Quantitative Business Analysis) course by showing them how to use Excel functions to produce regression analysis, make forecasts, create charts, and analyze information.
- Improved students' understanding of data analysis, variance analysis, and statistical inference.
- Tutored students' grades increased an average of +10%.

National Society of Leadership and Success

August 2012 - May 2013

Treasurer

- Successfully managed the club's budget and finances for specific events and fundraisers.
- Contributed to the success and growth of the organization by actively participating in online conference calls, initiating new ideas during Executive Board meetings, and making accurate forecasts of future expenses.

Aramark

August 2006 - May 2010; January 2012 - September 2012

Catering Captain

- Observed, managed, and directed employees during catering events.
- Coordinated large catering events of 1000 people by delegating tasks and responsibilities of associates.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2005 - May 2006

Cashier

McDonald's

- Managed financial transactions.
- Served a wide variety of people and cultures in a fast-paced working environment.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient with all Microsoft Office programs including an in-depth understanding of all excel functions.
- Fluent in speaking, reading, and writing Bulgarian.
- Broad understanding in speaking, reading, and writing Spanish.